welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we're going to be looking at the
我们将要观看的视频是
text tool in and learn how to
中的文本工具并学习如何
create and modify text within go
在GO中创建和修改文本
ahead and locate your text tool it's
在前面找到你的文本工具
going to be maybe the letter A icon and
可能会是字母A图标和
with this icon set if we hover over we
如果我们将鼠标悬停在我们的上方
can see the shortcut key to get into
可以看到快捷键进入
this is T T for text so if we're in the
这是文本的T T 所以如果我们在
move tool for example we can hit the T
移动工具例如 我们可以按T键
key on our keyboard to quickly get into
键盘上的按键可以快速进入
this tool and also once we're in the
这个工具 而且一旦我们进入
tool we see some different options for
工具我们看到了一些不同的选项
it right down here we see what type of
就在这里 我们看到了什么类型的
font it is this is a serif font the size
这是一种衬线字体的大小
currently is 60 and the color is black
当前为60 颜色为黑色
and there's some different options here
这里有一些不同的选择
as well
也是
so that means when we go to create this
所以这意味着当我们去创造这个
if we just left-click in here it creates
如果我们只在此处左键单击 它会创建
these four boxes this is our sort of our
这四个盒子这是我们的那种
dynamic text box and we can just start
动态文本框 我们可以开始
typing in right now we type our text and
现在我们输入我们的文本 然后
sure enough it's the color it's black
果然是黑色的
it's using this serif font and the size
它使用这种衬线字体和大小
is 60 now if we want to change it or
现在是60岁 如果我们想改变它 或者
change any part of it we can select
更改它的任何我们可以选择的部分
maybe if we want this is to be larger we
也许如果我们想要这个更大一点的话
just left click and hold to select those
只需左键单击并按住即可选择
two letters and then we can change the
两个字母 然后我们就可以更改
size up here by going plus and minus and
在这里用正负和
so we can make just those larger if we
所以我们可以把它们做得更大如果我们
want just a certain letter to be much
只想要某个字母就多了
larger we select that letter by
较大的字母我们按以下顺序选择
left-clicking and dragging till it has a
左键单击并拖动 直到它具有
box around it and then we can use plus
框住它 然后我们可以使用加号
and minus up here to change we don't use
减去这里 改变我们不使用的
the plus and minus over here because
这里的正负是因为
that's going to change the entire
这将改变整个
selection or it's going to change the
选择 否则它将改变
attributes for the next text box that we
的下一个文本框的属性
create so whatever is selected is going
创建以使所选内容成为现实
to be what's changed up here we can also
为了在这里改变 我们还可以
double click and just type in a value so
双击并只需键入一个值即可
150 we can make a giant s there notice
我们可以在那里做一个巨型S的预告
something you want to pay attention to
你想要注意的事情
is if you bring in an image and I have
就是如果你带来一张图片 我有
one loaded in here actually before we do
一辆在我们之前就装上了
this I want to call your attention to
我想提醒你注意这一点
the layers when we created this we've
当我们创建这些层时 我们已经
created a text layer on top of our white
在白色的顶部创建了一个文本层
background which means if we ever want
这意味着如果我们想要
to we can get back in here and edit it
我们可以回到这里来编辑它
say we're using the move tool or maybe
假设我们正在使用移动工具 或者可能
we select something we want to get back
我们选择了一些我们想要的东西
in and edit this text all we have to do
编辑这篇文章 我们所要做的就是
is click on the text tool and then click
是点击文本工具 然后点击
in here and we can erase
在这里 我们可以擦除
and start typing in something else if we
然后开始输入其他东西 如果我们
want to do we can also resize the text
想要做的话我们还可以调整文本大小
box by dragging these handles over here
框中 将这些手柄拖到这里
and if we want to move it around we
如果我们想要移动它 我们
could use the move tool but you can also
可以使用移动工具 但您也可以
hold down the Alt key on your keyboard
按住键盘上的Alt键
and just click somewhere within the text
只需点击文本中的某个位置
box and drag this moves the entire text
框并拖动此选项可移动整个文本
box and again to resize the text box you
框 然后再次调整文本框的大小
can hover to the top or the sides and
可以悬停到顶部或两侧 并
notice if you do resize it since this is
注意 如果您确实调整了它的大小 因为这是
a dynamic text box it will kind of push
一个动态文本框 它会像推送一样
the the text to the next portion of the
将文本添加到下一部分
box that makes sense it won't run off
有意义的盒子 它不会跑掉
the side but it will run off the tops
侧面 但它将从顶部流出
and the bottoms okay I'm going to go to
还有屁股好的 我要去
this image here because this is a quite
这张图片是因为这是一张
a large image we can see it's like five
一张我们可以看到的大图 大概有五张
thousand pixels by thirty five hundred
千像素乘以三千五百
pixels and it's 300 dpi so if we grab
像素是300dpi 所以如果我们
the same text tool with the same
相同的文本工具和相同的
settings the 60 size and we click and we
将大小设置为60 然后点击 我们
start typing in that same thing notice
开始输入相同的内容通知
it's much much smaller it appears to be
它看起来要小得多
smaller and that's because the image is
更小 那是因为图像是
so much larger so relative to this image
相对于这张图片要大得多
size the text appears to be small but it
大小文本看起来很小 但它
is still the same size as it was over
仍然和它结束时一样大
here at least before we started messing
至少在我们开始捣乱之前
with it so to change the size again we
有了它 为了再次改变尺寸 我们
can come over here and just change the
可以到这里来 只需更改
size of the text we can click in here
我们可以点击此处的文本大小
and type in 150 and get some larger text
然后输入150 得到一些较大的文本
we might also want to change the color
我们可能还想更改颜色
if I move this over top of the green
如果我把这个移到果岭上方
leaf by holding down the Alt key and I
通过按住Alt键和我来选择树叶
drag it on top of the leaf now it's hard
把它拖到树叶顶上 现在很硬
to see that so we might want a lighter
所以我们可能需要一个打火机
color text we can click over here and
彩色文本 我们可以点击这里和
change the color we can change it to
更改我们可以更改的颜色
something maybe like a light blue and
可能是淡蓝色的 然后
then we go okay now that stands out a
那么我们现在就走好了 这是一个突出的
little bit better again the color change
颜色的变化又好了一点
is happening here in the text options
在文本选项中正在发生
and not the color selector here where we
而不是我们这里的颜色选择器
would change it for our brush so make
会把它换成我们的刷子 所以让
sure you pay attention to that but we
你当然会注意到这一点 但我们
can bring in some text so maybe I'll
我可以带来一些文本 所以也许我会
come back here well I can do it right
回来吧 好的 我能做好
here if we want to draw a text box
如果我们要绘制一个文本框 请在此处
another thing we can do is create a new
我们可以做的另一件事是创建一个新的
text box by left clicking and holding
通过左键单击并按住文本框
and dragging that down then we can
把它拖下去 我们就可以
create a specific area
创建特定区域
to keep our text within and I have a on
把我们的文字保留在里面 我有一个
my desktop a file just a text file of
我的桌面只是一个文本文件
some sample text it looks like this just
一些示例文本 它看起来就像这样
sample just Latin I believe satin satin
样品是拉丁文的 我相信是绸缎的
sample Latin text and I could copy it I
样本拉丁文本和我可以复制它我
could just highlight it all and
只需突出显示这一切
right-click and go copy and then bring
右键单击并复制 然后带上
it in here right-click and go paste to
它在这里右击并粘贴到
get that text in here but I'm gonna go
把短信发进来 但我要走了
ctrl Z oh it's not let us ctrl Z because
Ctrl Z哦不是让我们Ctrl Z因为
something we could also do is when we
我们还可以做的一件事是当我们
have our text box created I can right
创建我们的文本框我可以对吗
click and I can go open text file and
点击 我就可以打开文本文件
that lets me choose a text file on my
这让我可以在我的
computer that already has text in it and
已经有文本的计算机 并且
it will bring it in text cannot be
它会将其带入文本中不能
rendered it is likely too big please
弄得太大了 请给我
make sure please make it shorter or use
请确保将其缩短或使用
a smaller font so this is just a notice
较小的字体 所以这只是一个通知
saying it's running off the edge but
说它已经走到了边缘 但是
what I could do I wonder if it brought
我能做什么 我想知道它是否带来了
it all in if I resize this so there's
如果我调整它的大小 就会有
more text under here that I can access
此处下方有更多我可以访问的文本
by just resizing this box to display all
只需调整此框的大小即可显示所有
of the text so that's a nice warning
所以这是一个很好的警告
that it gave me that I was cutting off
它让我意识到我正在切断
some of the text I'm moving this by
我要移动的一些文本
holding down the Alt key I've mentioned
按住我提到的Alt键
that a few times but we could also grab
有几次 但我们也可以抓住
the move tool and it moves just like we
移动工具 它会像我们一样移动
would expect any other layer so here we
会期待任何其他的层 所以在这里我们
have three layers we have this blue text
有三层 我们有这个蓝色文本
this blacks black text and then also the
这会使黑色文本变为黑色 然后还会显示
actual image so I can set this to move
实际图像 所以我可以将其设置为移动
active layer and make sure I'm selected
活动层并确保我已被选中
on the layer I want to move and I can
在我想要移动的层上 我可以
just left click and move this without
只需左键点击并移动此图标即可
having to press the Alt key I want to
我必须按Alt键才能
show something here we can this turn off
在这里展示一些我们可以关闭的东西
just like we would any layer we can turn
就像我们可以转向的任何一层一样
off and view this without one of the
关闭并查看此内容 而不使用
layers so we could also I'll move this
层层 所以我们也可以 我会移动这个
out of the way because I want to show
别挡道 因为我想展示
something we can do if we want to edit
一些我们可以做的事情 如果我们想编辑
something in here we get back into the
这里的一些东西我们回到了
text tool to do an edit it's not the
进行编辑的文本工具它不是
selection tool if we try to select the
选择工具 如果我们尝试选择
text it's going to select the pixels of
它将要选择的像素的文本
that text on that text layer but if we
文本层上的文本 但如果我们
want to get in and edit this we can
想要进入并编辑这个 我们可以
select it we could go to select all we
选择它 我们可以去选择我们所有的
can select it with or click inside of it
可以使用选择它 也可以在其内部单击
it what I mean to say with the text tool
这就是我想用文本工具说的话
were active and then we can make changes
都处于活动状态 然后我们就可以进行更改
so under here there's this justification
所以在这里有这样一个理由
so
所以
we want all this text to be centered we
我们希望所有这些文本都居中
can click here to Center all the text we
可以单击此处居中显示我们的所有文本
can put it in sort of a paragraph format
我可以把它放在一种段落格式中
with the edges aligned so the edges all
使边缘对齐 使所有边缘都
the text runs to the edges and it
文本排到了边上 它
creates some spacing to create sort of a
创建一些间距 以创建一种
more of a block of text we can do right
更多的是我们可以正确处理的文本块
justified or left justified we could
正当性或左正当性我们可以
indent this first word by we can hover
将第一个单词缩进到我们可以悬停的位置
over and read what these are but this
读一读这些是什么 但这是
top one is the indent and we can indent
上面的一个是缩进 我们可以缩进
that first word by making this a little
第一个词 把这个写得有点
bit larger or we can type in a quite a
大一点 或者我们可以输入一个相当大的
large value and see how that indents it
较大的值 并查看它是如何缩进的
again it's going to be different
再一次 这将是不同的
depending on what size image you're
取决于你的图片的大小
using so a 800 pixels is usually quite a
使用这样的800像素通常是相当大的
large indentation but since this is a
大缩进 但由于这是一个
large image it doesn't really add this a
大图 它并没有真正增加这一点
little bit dramatic anyway the next one
不管怎样 下一次有一点戏剧性
here this is the line spacing and the
这里是行距和
font spacing or the letter spacing so
字体间距或字母间距So
this is what you do like remember when
这就是你喜欢做的 记住当
you're in school and you had to write an
你在上学 你必须写一封信
essay and you had to have like five
散文 你必须得有五个
pages you'd like stretch the the spacing
你想要的页面拉长了空格
between the lines that's exactly what
字里行间就是这样
this tool here does and if you really
这个工具可以做到这一点 如果你真的
want to get creative you could adjust
想要变得有创意 你可以调整
the spacing between letters anyway
不管怎样 字母之间的间距
that's what it's lets you do very very
这就是它让你做的非常非常
useful if you're working with text and
如果您正在处理文本和
you want to kind of give it that added
你想给它加点什么
dimension and fill in certain areas yeah
标注尺寸并填写某些区域是的
that's but all we're going to use
这就是我们要用到的全部
there's this there's this editor here
有这样一个编辑在这里
you can go use editor you can adjust the
您可以使用编辑器 您可以调整
text in here as well and edit it and it
文本也在这里 并编辑它和它
will edit it on here and you can do some
我会在这里编辑它 你可以做一些
of these same tools but it's sort of
同样的工具 但这是一种
redundant because you can change it you
多余的 因为你可以改变它
can just come in and change it in real
可以直接进入并真实地改变它
time on here but just know there is an
时间在这里 但要知道有一个
editor if you prefer to work that way to
如果您愿意以这种方式工作 请编辑
change the font well we can select or we
很好地更改字体 我们可以选择或我们
can change the font over here this will
我可以更改这里的字体 这将
just change all of our font so we click
只需更改所有字体 这样我们就可以点击
and there's ways you can choose the way
有很多方法可以让你选择
that this font the way the fonts are
这种字体的字体是这样的
being displayed so you can come over
被展示出来这样你就可以过来
here and look at it in a grid instead we
在这里 在网格中查看它 而不是我们
can create it larger so we can get a
可以让它变得更大 这样我们就可以
better view of what these fonts look
更好地查看这些字体的外观
like and there's even a breakout if you
就像 甚至有突破 如果你
do this last one it's kind of nice if
做最后一个 如果
you're working with fonts a lot you can
您使用的字体很多 可以
add over here so that the font selection
在这里添加 以便选择的字体
comes over here on this side instead so
而是从这边走过来 所以
just like we had our layers was the
就像我们有自己的层次一样
we were looking at before now we have a
我们之前看过的现在我们有一个
new window a new font dialog or tool box
新建窗口新建字体对话框或工具箱
just for selecting fonts and browsing
仅用于选择字体和浏览
through fonts that are installed on our
通过安装在
system and that's exactly what these are
系统 这就是这些
just fonts installed on the system not
只有安装在系统上的字体不会
special fonts that come with
随附的特殊字体
necessarily so if a fonts installed in
如果一个字体安装在
your system it should be able to get
您的系统应该能够
pulled in and appear in this list okay
拉进来并出现在这个列表中好的
this is the last thing I was going to
这是我最不想做的事
show you if we grab the brush tool let's
如果我们抓住画笔工具 让我们展示一下
go back to our layers over here and
回到我们这里的层级 然后
let's draw if we grab the let's grab a
我们抽签吧 如果我们赢了我们就赢了
brush and it's just black right now we
现在只有一片漆黑 我们
want to draw well first of all we can't
想要画得好首先我们不能
draw over here nothing is happening
把车开过来 什么事也没发生
because we're on this text layer and
因为我们在这个文本层上
notice this layer has a little a on it
请注意 这一层上有一个小a
showing us that this is a text layer
向我们显示这是一个文本层
which is what lets us be able to get in
这就是我们能够进入的原因
here and make changes to it after the
在这里 并在
fact we can draw on this so if I wanted
事实上我们可以利用这一点 所以如果我想
to do some drawing on top of these
在这些上面画一些画
letters I can do that but that changed
信件我可以这样做 但那已经改变了
this now to I'm not sure what it's
现在我不知道这是什么
called but it's a different layer it's
但这是一个不同的层面
not a text layer anymore which means if
不再是文本层 这意味着如果
I want to come back to the text tool to
我想回到文本工具来
make an edit and click in here it's
进行编辑并点击此处
going to bring up this dialog that says
我要打开这个对话框 上面写着
the layer selected is a text layer but
所选的层是文本层 但
has not been modified using or has been
未使用修改或已被修改
modified using other tools so we can
使用其他工具进行修改 以便我们可以
either create a new layer to edit on top
创建要在顶部进行编辑的新图层
of this or we can edit it but if we do
或者我们可以编辑它 但如果我们这样做了
we're going to lose or does it say it
我们要输了 还是它说了算
basically it'll discard yeah discard all
基本上它会丢弃是的丢弃所有
the modifications we've made so if I go
我们所做的修改 所以如果我去
to edit that's gone now I can edit the
要编辑已消失的内容 现在我可以编辑
text but all the drawing I did on top of
文本 但我在上面做的所有图画
there is gone so it's a good idea it's a
已经没有了 所以这是个好主意
I recommend just keeping your text
我建议你只保留你的短信
layers as text and then if you want to
将层转换为文本 然后如果您想
draw something go ahead and add in a new
画一些东西 然后添加一个新的
layer and draw on top of that new layer
层并在该新层的顶部进行绘制
you can make it a transparent layer oops
你可以把它变成透明的一层
but that's what I would recommend doing
但这就是我推荐的做法
instead of trying to draw within your
与其试图在你的
text layers hopefully I found this video
文字层希望我能找到这段视频
informative I kind of rented that
很有见地 我租了那个
quickly but we are gonna touch on more
很快 但我们会触及更多
advanced options for making text look
用于使文本看起来像的高级选项
pretty you can do text a path and you
很漂亮 你可以做文本 一个路径 你
can do some pretty cool things adding
我可以做一些很酷的事情
texture and dimension and 3d text and
纹理和尺寸以及3D文本和
all kinds of stuff like that but I'm
诸如此类的事情 但我
going to end this video here go and
在这里结束这段视频 开始
leave your questions and comments below
在下面留下您的问题和评论
if you have an
如果你有一个
and we'll catch you in the next video
我们会在下一段视频中看到你